See,see, see, see.
(Penny:)Just now you expressed
your feelings to my face.
(Penny:)How come you could do that
with me, but not with Raj?
(Lucy:)I don't know your e-mail.
(Penny:)You know what the worst part is?
You're sitting here, perfectly happy
(Penny:)and he's at home, a blubbering mess.
(Lucy:)Oh, I thought you said he was okay.
(Penny:)I also said I was getting you water,
but look at me still standing here.
(Penny:)You know, I may be a bad waitress,
but you are a bad person.
(Penny:)Now, you want to hear the specials?
-80, you can never take it off?
-No.
(Raj:)Not even to sleep?
(Penny:)No.
(Howard:)So, you're just an idiot?
(Leonard:)It's called proving a point.
Is the point you're an idiot?